[{"id": 2, "topic": "Python", "question": "How can yu define a dtype in a structured array - Python? Give an example", "hint": null, "answer": "You can define a structured array writing: dtype = np.dtype([(np.float32, np.int32)]). ", "author_id": "jan", "timestamp": "2024-05-30 10:22:45", "flags": {}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 4, "topic": "Python", "question": "What language is Python implemented in? ", "hint": null, "answer": "C Programming Langugae ", "author_id": "jan", "timestamp": "2024-06-09 12:34:17", "flags": {}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 5, "topic": "Python", "question": "Python collection to add elements to an array from either side ? ", "hint": null, "answer": "Deque ", "author_id": "jan", "timestamp": "2024-06-09 12:35:29", "flags": {}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 1, "topic": "Python", "question": "What are python dicts used for? ", "hint": null, "answer": "Dicts are used to store data which can be mapped like a key-value pair, (\"think dictionaries\") and can also be used as frequency counters. ", "author_id": "jan", "timestamp": "2024-05-30 10:21:10", "flags": {"right": 1, "show_answer": 2, "wrong": 1}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 3, "topic": "Hey", "question": "Wassu", "hint": null, "answer": "ssup", "author_id": "jan", "timestamp": "2024-06-04 22:59:59", "flags": {"right": 1, "show_answer": 1}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 6, "topic": "Python", "question": "How to print a statement", "hint": null, "answer": "print(\"<your_statement\")", "author_id": "_jan", "timestamp": "2024-06-09 22:53:45", "flags": {}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 7, "topic": "Python", "question": "What are defaultdicts", "hint": "dicts without keys", "answer": "defaultdicts are used to create key-value pairs in a dict without explicitly having to give key-names, and a specific value data-type.", "author_id": "_jan", "timestamp": "2024-06-09 23:09:54", "flags": {}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 8, "topic": "Python", "question": "Read the following work on docstring! ", "hint": "", "answer": "https://github.com/norvig/pytudes/blob/main/ipynb/DocstringFixpoint.ipynb", "author_id": "_jan", "timestamp": "2024-06-09 23:29:50", "flags": {}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 9, "topic": "Python", "question": "Guido's full name", "hint": "No hints available!", "answer": "Guido Van Rossum", "author_id": "_jan", "timestamp": "2024-06-09 23:32:40", "flags": {"right": 2, "show_answer": 2}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 12, "topic": "python", "question": "awrgaerwth", "hint": "qathqethqetjh", "answer": "qetjhqetjqertj", "author_id": "jkl", "timestamp": "2024-06-12 20:32:56", "flags": {"wrong": 2, "hint_used": 2, "right": 1}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 11, "topic": "test", "question": "AERG", "hint": "AERG", "answer": "aerbhaerh", "author_id": "jkl", "timestamp": "2024-06-12 19:34:16", "flags": {"wrong": 3, "show_answer": 6, "right": 9, "hint_used": 7}, "next_review_date": null}, {"id": 10, "topic": "python", "question": "what are ds", "hint": "loog gpt", "answer": "awrgawrh", "author_id": "jkl", "timestamp": "2024-06-12 19:33:56", "flags": {"right": 5, "show_answer": 10, "wrong": 7, "hint_used": 9}, "next_review_date": null}]